gamez.com 2005-04-03

# Gamez.com - Privacy Policy Information

| Main Options  
  
User Options  
  
Submit Content  

Cheats/Guides  
  
Content  
Sites  
  
Downloads  
  
Images  
  
About Us  

|   
|   

| | Privacy Policy Information  
  
---  
Privacy Policy  

Gamez.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.  
  
Server Logging  
  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information for audience analysis.  
  
Personal Information  
  
We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of you as a user of this Website. This Website does not collect Personal Information about you except for information that you voluntarily provide (for example, when you submit an email to us with comments about our web site or products reviewed on the web site and you do not specifically indicate that the information contained within is to be considered confidential or provide answers to a voluntary readership survey.)  
  
We consider the following to be Personal Information: your name, address, phone number, date of birth, job, personal interests, credit card information, your e-mail address and data about the pages you visited on this Website.  
  
Links to Other Sites  
  
This site contains links to other sites. Gamez.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
  
Online Surveys  
  
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.  
  
Advertising  
  
We use outside advertising companies to display advertising on our site. Ads may contain cookies and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site.  
  
For privacy information regarding the advertising companies we use, click on the following links:  

Third Party Cookies  
  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.  
  
Public Forums  
  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
  
Security  
  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However in the event of a security breach of this site please note that no personal information of the visitors would be accessible online as none are stored locally.  
  
Supplementation Information  
  
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.  
  
Contacting the Web Site  
  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [Contact Us](http://gamez.com/sage/feedback.x?to=privacy).  

| | Login  
  
---
